## ZAHRA NURDYANI

Bandung, Indonesia | zahranurdyani11@gmail.com | +6281214872594 | www.linkedin.com/in/zahra-nurdyani-b03b2a237

### **EXECUTIVE SUMMARY**

I have an interest in application development, analysis, and planning activities. I'm passionate about developing experience and knowledge. Attention to detail has become my forte. I'm an inquisitive person that enjoys learning new things and finding solutions to existing situations. I'm ability to adapt and build a stable atmosphere. I'm a fast phase person who can work precisely under pressure.

### **EDUCATION**

#### **SMA TELKOM BANDUNG**

July 2017 - June 2020

# Major in Science

- 3<sup>rd</sup> Runner Up of National Scientific Writing Competition "Bakti Formica Bangsa XXI" Universitas Pendidikan Indonesia
- 3<sup>rd</sup> Runner Up of Industrial Green Competition Telkom University 2018.
- 3<sup>rd</sup> Runner Up of Industrial Green Competition Telkom University 2017.

### **TELKOM UNIVERSITY**

September 2020 - Now

## Major in Diploma Information System

GPA: 3.97 / 4.0

- Awardee of One Pipe Education System (OPES)
- Participant of Program Kreativitas Mahasiswa (PKM) 2021
- Participant of Program Kreativitas Mahasiswa (PKM) 2022
- Participant of GEMASTIK XIV 2021
- Finalist of National Scientific Writing Competition "Gebyar Farmasi 2021" Universitas Andalas

### WORK EXPERIENCE

### DIREKTORAT KEMAHASISWAAN UNIVERSITAS TELKOM

May 2021 - July 2021

### Liaison Officer Internship

- Manage and assist Telkom University faculty staff to upload or input data SIMKATMAWA (Sistem Informasi Manajemen Pemeringkatan Kemahasiswaan)
- Monitoring and ensure complete data
- Reminded Telkom University faculty staff to upload or input data SIMKATMAWA (Sistem Informasi Manajemen Pemeringkatan Kemahasiswaan)

### PT AERO SYSTEMS INDONESIA

August 2022 - June 2023

# Front End Developer Internship

- Develop application using React Typescript, Material UI, and '@andrydharmawan' component
- Integrate pages with database APIs
- Make improvements if there are bugs that interfere with application activities
- Monitoring and ensure all features and pages according to user requirements can run smoothly
- Make the required validation on a particular page
- Make the required features according to user requirements

## ORGANIZATION AND SOCIAL PROJECT

#### PERMIB FREEDOM IN CREATIVITY

# December 2020 - May 2021

### Secretary of Event Division

- Organized and record the results of routine division meetings
- Organized the regular meeting schedule of the event division
- Analyze and plan the event
- Make an event timeline from the beginning of the activity to the end
- Coordinated all performance
- Monitoring and ensure the event runs smoothly
- Manage time of the event

### **INDUSTRIAL LECTURE D3 SISTEM INFORMASI**

December 2021 - January 2022

### **Public Relation Division**

- Design virtual background for zoom meeting
- Design poster for social media and advertising

**WARMING UP** January 2022 - January 2023

# Chief of Operation and Public Relation Division

- Design and implement business strategies, plans, and procedures
- Oversee daily operations of the company and the work of (IT, marketing)
- Write and submit reports to CEO
- Lead employees to encourage maximum performance
- Evaluate performance by analyzing and interpreting data
- Design social media content

#### SKILLS AND OTHERS

- Program Management: SDLC (Software Development Life Cycle), Jira
- Tools and Frameworks: Java script, React (18.1.0), Material UI, HTML, CSS, PHP, Database (MySQL), Figma
- Certifications: Google Cloud Fundamentals Core Infrastructure (2022)